<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lancer Frame Builder</string>
    <string name="everest_traits"><b>INITIATIVE</b>\n1/scene the Everest may take any quick action as a free action.\n\n<b>REPLACEABLE PARTS</b>\nWhile resting, the Everest can be repaired at a rate of 1 Repair per 1 structure damage, instead of 2 Repairs.</string>
    <string name="everest_core_power">HYPERSPEC FUEL INJECTOR\nPower Up\nActive (1CP), Protocol\n\nFor the rest of this scene, you gain +1 Accuracy on all
        attacks, checks, and saves; additionally, 1/turn, you can BOOST as a free action.</string>
    <string name="everest_description"><b>EVEREST</b>\n\nA balanced mech for those seeking a jack of all trades.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_traits"><b>GRAPPLE CABLE</b>\nThe Blackbeard can grapple targets within Range 5. If
the GRAPPLE is successful, the Blackbeard is
immediately pulled to a space adjacent the target
by the most direct path. If there are no suitable
spaces, the grapple breaks and the Blackbeard
does not move.\n\nLOCK/KILL SUBSYSTEM\nWhile grappling, the Blackbeard can BOOST and
use reactions.\n\nEXPOSED REACTOR\nThe Blackbeard receives +1 Difficulty on ENGINEERING
checks and saves.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_core_power">OMNI-HARPOON\nActive (1CP), Quick Action\n\nThis system fires grappling harpoons at any
number of targets within Range 5 and line of sight.
Affected characters that fail a HULL save take
2d6 kinetic damage, are knocked PRONE, and then pulled
adjacent to you, or as close as possible. They
become IMMOBILIZED until the end of their next
turn. If they pass the save, they take half damage
and are otherwise unaffected.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_description"><b>BLACKBEARD</b>\n\nA close range melee-oriented mech with powerful grappling abilites.</string>
    <string name="sherman_traits"><b>SUPERIOR REACTOR</b>\nThe Sherman gains +1 Accuracy on all ENGINEERING
checks and saves.\n\n<b>MATHUR STOP</b>\nWhen the Sherman clears all heat, you may choose
to receive heat equal to half its Heat Cap, putting it
in the Danger Zone.\n\n<b>VENT HEAT</b>\nWhen you STABILIZE the Sherman or it exceeds its
HEAT CAP, it benefits from soft cover until the start
of your next turn.</string>
    <string name="sherman_core_power">COREBURN PROTOCOL\nActive (1CP), Protocol\n\nYour ZF4 SOLIDCORE immediately gains 3
CHARGES, to a maximum of 4; additionally, for the
rest of this scene, STABILIZE generates 2 charges
instead of 1, and all terrain, objects, and
deployables take 10 AP energy damage per charge on hit.</string>
    <string name="sherman_description"><b>SHERMAN</b>\n\nA long range laser-wielding frame that uses its own heat to its advantage.</string>
    <string name="antiMaterialRifle">ANTI-MATERIAL RIFLE\nAccurate, AP, Loading, Ordnance\n[Heavy Rifle] Range 20, 2d6 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="assaultRifle">ASSAULT RIFLE\nReliable 2\n[Main Rifle] Range 10, 1d6 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="chargedBlade">CHARGED BLADE\nAP\n[Main Melee] Threat 1, 1d3+3 Energy</string>
    <string name="cyclonePulseRifle">CYCLONE PULSE RIFLE\nAccurate, Loading, Reliable 5\n[Superheavy Rifle] Range 15, 3d6+3 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="heavyChargedBlade">HEAVY CHARGED BLADE\nAP\n[Heavy Melee] Threat 1, 1d6+3 Energy</string>
    <string name="heavyMachineGun">HEAVY MACHINE GUN\nInaccurate\n[Heavy Cannon] Range 8, 2d6+4 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="heavyMeleeWeapon">HEAVY MELEE WEAPON\n-\n[Heavy Melee] Threat 1, 2d6+1 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="howitzer">HOWITZER\nArcing, Inaccurate, Loading, Ordnance\n[Heavy Cannon] Range 20/Blast 2, 2d6 Explosive</string>
    <string name="missileRack">MISSILE RACK\nLoading\n[Auxiliary Launcher] Range 10/Blast 1, 1d3+1 Explosive</string>
    <string name="mortar">MORTAR\nArcing, Inaccurate\n[Main Cannon] Range 15/Blast 1, 1d6+1 Explosive</string>
    <string name="hunterKillerNexus">HUNTER-KILLER NEXUS\nSmart\n[Main Nexus] Range 10, 1d6 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="lightNexus">LIGHT NEXUS\nSmart\n[Auxiliary Nexus] Range 10, 1d3 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="pistol">PISTOL\nReliable 1\n[Auxiliary CQB] Range 5/Threat 3, 1d3 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="progressiveKnife">PROGRESSIVE KNIFE\nOverkill\n[Auxiliary Melee] Threat 1, 1d3+1 Energy</string>
    <string name="rpg">ROCKET-PROPELLED GRENADE\nLoading, Ordnance\n[Main Launcher] Range 10/Blast 2, 1d6+1 Explosive</string>
    <string name="shotgun">SHOTGUN\n-\n[Main CQB] Range 5/Threat 3, 1d6 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="tacticalKnife">TACTICAL KNIFE\nThrown 3\[Auxiliary Melee] Threat 1, 1d3+1 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="tacticalMeleeWeapon">TACTICAL MELEE WEAPON\n-\n[Main Melee] Threat 1, 1d6+2 Kinetic</string>
    <string name="thermalLance">THERMAL LANCE\n2 Heat (Self)\n[Heavy Cannon] Line 10, 1d6+3 Energy</string>
    <string name="thermalPistol">THERMAL PISTOL\n-\n[Auxiliary CQB] Line 5, 2 Energy</string>
    <string name="thermalRifle">THERMAL RIFLE\nAP\n[Main Rifle] Range 5, 1d3+2 Energy</string>
    <string name="comcponAI">COMP/CON ASSISTANT UNIT [2 SP, AI, Unique]\n\nYour mech has a basic comp/con unit, granting it
the AI tag. The comp/con can speak to you and has
a personality, but, unlike an NHP, is not truly capable
of independent thought. It is obedient to you alone.
You can give control of your mech to its comp/con
as a protocol, allowing your mech to act
independently on your turn with its own set of
actions. Unlike other AIs, a mech controlled by a
comp/con has no independent initiative and requires
direct input. Your mech will follow basic courses of
action (defend this area, attack this enemy, protect
me, etc.) to the best of its ability, or will act to defend
itself if its instructions are complete or it receives no
further guidance. You can issue new commands at
the start of your turn as long as you are within 50
and have the means to communicate with your
mech. Comp/con units are not true NHPs and thus
cannot enter cascade.</string>
    <string name="paintJob">CUSTOM PAINT JOB [1 SP, Unique]\n\nWhen your mech takes structure damage, roll 1d6.
    On a 6, you return to 1 HP and ignore the damage
    – the hit simply ‘scratched your paint’.
    This system can only be used once between full
    repairs, and is not a valid target for system
    destruction.
</string>
<string name="exCompartment">EXPANDED COMPARTMENT [1 SP, Unique]\n\nYour mech has space for one additional non-
    MECH character or object of Size 1/2 to ride as a
    passenger in the cockpit. While inside the mech,
    they cannot suffer any effect from outside or be
    targeted by attacks, as if they were a pilot. You
    can hand over or take back control to or from
    them at the start of any turn (following the same
    rules as pilot and AI), but if they take over the
    controls from you, the mech becomes IMPAIRED
    and SLOWED to reflect the lack of appropriate
    licenses and integration.
    </string>
<string name="manipulators">MANIPULATORS [1 SP, Unique]\n\nYour mech has an extra set of limbs. They are too
    small to have any combat benefit, but allow the mech
    to interact with objects that would otherwise be too
    small or sensitive (e.g., pilot-sized touch pads).
    </string>
<string name="smokeCharges">PATTERN-A SMOKE CHARGES [2 SP, Limited 3, Unique]\n\nYou may spend a charge from this system for one
    of the following effects:
    • Smoke grenade (Grenade, Range 5, Blast 2): All
    characters and objects within the blast area
    benefit from soft cover until the end of your next
    turn, at which point the smoke disperses.
    • Smoke mine (Mine, Blast 3): This mine detonates
    when any allied character moves over or
    adjacent to it. All characters and objects within
    the burst area benefit from soft cover until the
    end of the detonating character’s next turn, at
    which point the smoke disperses.
    </string>
<string name="depCover">PATTERN-A JERICHO DEPLOYABLE COVER [2 SP, Deployable, Unique, Quick Action]\n\nAs a quick action, you may deploy two sections of
    SIZE 1 hard cover in free spaces adjacent to the
    user and to each other. Each section is an object
    with 5 EVASION and 10 HP that can be targeted and
    destroyed individually. It is one full action to pick
    up both sections of cover once they have been
    deployed.
    Repairing the system while resting or repairing
    restores both sections.
    </string>
<string name="hexCharges">PATTERN-B HEX CHARGES [2 SP, Limited 3, Unique]\n\nYou may spend a charge from this system for one
    of the following effects:
    • Frag grenade (Grenade, Range 5, Blast 1): All
    characters within the blast area must pass an
    AGILITY save or take 1d6 Explosive damage. On a successful
    save, they take half damage.
    • Explosive mine (Mine, Burst 1): All characters
    within the burst area must pass an AGILITY save
    or take 2d6 Explosive damage. On a successful save, they take
    half damage.
    </string>
<string name="personalizations">PERSONALIZATIONS [1 SP, Unique]\n\nYour mech gains +2 HP and, in consultation with
    the GM, you may establish a minor modification
    you have made to your mech.
    This mod has no numerical benefit beyond the
    additional HP it grants, but could provide other
    useful effects. If the GM agrees that this mod
    would help with either a pilot or mech skill check,
    you gain +1 ACCURACY for that check.
    </string>
<string name="stableStructure">STABLE STRUCTURE [2 SP, Unique]\n\nYour mech gains +1 ACCURACY on saves to avoid PRONE or
    KNOCKBACK.
    </string>
<string name="turretDrones">TURRET DRONES [2 SP, Limited 3, Unique, Quick Action]\n\nDrone (SIZE 1/2, 5 HP, 10 E-DEFENSE, 10 EVASION,
    TAGS: DRONE)
    Expend a charge to deploy a turret drone that
    attaches to any object or surface within SENSORS
    and line of sight. Gain the TURRET ATTACK
    reaction, which can be taken once for each
    deployed turret drone. Turret drones cannot be
    recalled and expire at the end of the scene.
    </string>
<string name="t1shield">TYPE-I SHIELD [2 SP, Shield, Unique, Protocol, 1 Heat (Self)]\n\n
    As a protocol, nominate a character within line of
    sight: all ranged or melee attacks that they make
    against you or that you make against them gain
    +2 DIFFICULTY until the start of your next turn.
    </string>
<string name="evaModule">EVA MODULE [1 SP, Unique]\n\nYour mech has a propulsion system suitable for
    use in low or zero gravity and underwater
    environments. In those environments, you can fly
    and are not SLOWED.
    </string>
<string name="jumpJets">RAPID BURST JUMP JET SYSTEM [2 SP, Unique]\n\nYou can fly when you BOOST; however, you must
    end the movement on the ground or another solid
    surface, or else immediately begin falling.
    </string>
<string name="flightSystem">TYPE-I FLIGHT SYSTEM [3 SP, Unique]\n\nYou can fly when you BOOST or make a standard
    move; however, you take SIZE +1 Heat at the end of
    any of your turns in which you fly this way.
    </string>
</resources>
